<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Solar System</string>
    <string name="sunInfo">Our Sun, the heart of the solar system, is a yellow dwarf star. Its
        gravity holds everything from small debris to large planets in orbit. Electric current
        in the Sun propagates the electromagnetic field in the form of solar winds.</string>
    <string name="mercuryInfo">Mercury, the closest planet to the Sun, is only slightly larger than
        Earth\'s Moon. Mercury is the fastest planet, completing its orbit around the Sun every
        88 Earth days.</string>
    <string name="venusInfo">Venus, the second planet from the Sun, spins in the opposite direction
        from most planets. Venus\'s thick atmosphere traps heat in a runaway greenhouse effect,
        making it the hottest planet in our solar system.</string>
    <string name="earthInfo">Earth, our home planet, is the only place we know of so far that\'s
        inhabited by intelligent life. It\'s also the only planet in our solar system with liquid
        water on the surface.</string>
    <string name="marsInfo">Mars is a dusty, cold, desert world with a very thin atmosphere. There
        is strong evidence Mars was wetter and warmer, with a thicker atmosphere billions of
        years ago.</string>
    <string name="jupiterInfo">Jupiter is more than twice as massive than the other planets of our
        solar system combined. The giant planet\'s Great Red spot is a centuries-old storm
        larger than the Earth.</string>
    <string name="saturnInfo">Adorned with a dazzling, complex system of icy rings, Saturn is
        unique in our solar system. The other giant planets have rings, but none are as spectacular
        as Saturn\'s.</string>
    <string name="uranusInfo">Uranus, the seventh planet from the sun, rotates at a nearly
        90-degree angle from the plane of its orbit. This unique tilt makes Uranus appear to spin
        on its side.</string>
    <string name="neptuneInfo">Neptune, the eighth and most distant planet orbiting our Sun,
        is dark, cold and whipped by supersonic winds. It was the first planet discovered through
        mathematical prediction.</string>
    <string name="plutoInfo">Pluto is a complex world of ice mountains and frozen plains. Once
        considered to be the ninth planet, Pluto is best known for a new classification called
        dwarf planets.</string>
</resources>